{
    "subject": "resource/Nicaragua",
    "predicate": "property/currency",
    "object": "resource/Nicaraguan_c\u00f3rdoba",
    "human_readable": "The currency of Nicaragua is Nicaraguan c\u00f3rdoba.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9590694308280945,
            "question": "Is the Nicaraguan c\u00f3rdoba a stable currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9133425354957581,
            "question": "What is the currency of Nicaragua?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8930349946022034,
            "question": "What is the value of one US dollar in Nicaraguan c\u00f3rdobas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8918224573135376,
            "question": "What are some ways that tourists can exchange their currency for Nicaraguan c\u00f3rdobas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8445709347724915,
            "question": "What is another name for the Nicaraguan c\u00f3rdoba?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8025836944580078,
            "question": "What are some factors that influence the value of the Nicaraguan c\u00f3rdoba?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7604976296424866,
            "question": "How does the Nicaraguan c\u00f3rdoba compare to other currencies in Central America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6916097402572632,
            "question": "How is the Nicaraguan c\u00f3rdoba represented symbolically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5808778405189514,
            "question": "Can you name a country that uses the c\u00f3rdoba as its currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49021005630493164,
            "question": "Has the Nicaraguan c\u00f3rdoba undergone any significant changes in its design over time?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of Nicaragua is Nicaraguan c\u00f3rdoba.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7552_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a country that uses the c\u00f3rdoba as its currency?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7552_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is the Nicaraguan c\u00f3rdoba represented symbolically?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7552_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the Nicaraguan c\u00f3rdoba compare to other currencies in Central America?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7552_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7552_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7552_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7552_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7552_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7552_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7552_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7552_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7552_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7552_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7552_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently indicate that the Nicaraguan c\u00f3rdoba is indeed the national currency of Nicaragua. This information is explicitly stated in multiple documents, such as `92.txt`, `96.txt`, and `73.txt`."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}